Yes! I'll keep you entertained in the Ikiri World whether you're asleep or awake!
I'm Geki, the Ikiiri, the Candy Man! Today, I'm here with the contents of my bag!
What a mess!
It's been quite a while since I introduced the contents of my bag on YouTube, right after I started about 3 years ago.
Today, I would like to introduce and check the contents of my bag after a long time!
Recently, I have been using a rather large bag to carry my makeup pouch in.
Here it is today! Ta-da!
It might be huge! It's called Maruni. It's cute!
It's double-colored, and the best part is that you can wear it over your shoulder!
I can carry it on my shoulder, so it's really useful!
I came here today with this Marni bag, so I'd like to show you what's inside!
First of all, a little makeup pouch!
I often change my makeup bag, but this one is just for now. I think it's just for the time being.
I think it's a novelty pouch that you get when you spend more than a certain amount of money at Viol. Just a little.
This and the clinic. This is also a novelty of cosmetics. Both of them.
I'm using a novelty pouch. This one has a particularly large capacity.
These are the first two pouches. This is a pouch for cosmetics.
In terms of pouches, this one is even cuter! So cute! I love Sanrio! This is KIKIRARARA!
I love Little Twin Stars.
I always carry this in my bag because I can put tissues in here and put things in there.
The tissues are Nose Celeb, by the way.
Let me introduce the contents of this bag.
First, eye drops!
These are a little bit tough and clumsy eye drops.
I was a little suspicious of the hay fever,
When they performed their new song "I really love you" for the first time at the Countdown TV live concert, they were in Tochigi, right?
It was in Tochigi, wasn't it? We were told that we would perform in front of a bamboo forest in Tochigi,
I was a little scared, so I thought it would be okay in the trees,
I was a little scared and wondered if I would be okay in the trees, so I bought some pollen drops at the station before I went.
I bought some eye drops for pollen at the station before I went. But they are my favorite because they feel sooooo good.
And there is one more eye drop.
This one is for my eyes, which tend to get a little bloodshot,
I got these at the ophthalmologist's. Don't you want them? I don't need this cut.
These are eye drops for dry eyes.
Two eye drops. And this.
Nonion. And this mouth spray.
I've already bought a lot of this at home.
And breath care.
I like these three colors.
I like the ones that come in three different flavors.
Lemon, Grape, and Peach.
And this breath care, always. Chewing Breath Care.
I carry it with me.
And this one.
This is perfume, but it's heavy to carry around a big bottle of perfume, so I replace it with this one,
But this leaked somewhere.
This one leaked somewhere.
It's so bad, but it's soaked up.
It doesn't smell bad, but I must have spilled it.
It smells good, but...
This is that white Savon, which is my favorite part.
I carry the one I'm replacing next to the course.
I also carry a spare accessory in case I forget it, though I usually only wear it for a photo shoot or something.
I carry a spare accessory in case I forget it.
This one that goes with any outfit.
One of these.
And I carry a light one.
The contents of this pouch are two tablets.
Next is a wallet!
I posted this on my insta-story.
I posted it on my insta-story, but it was on what day in March?
I can't remember at all!
I can't remember at all. 2 tablets is something like "What a day".
I heard it's good to get a new wallet.
I had time to go to a department store and buy something if I really liked it.
I fell in love with this one at first sight.
It's bi-colored inside.
Don't you just love bi-colors? Maybe I'm just attracted to bi-colors.
Maybe I'm attracted to bi-colors.
I had a dark pink purse last time.
I couldn't decide between light blue and pink, so I decided to go with light blue this time.
It's a little more grown-up, and it's a wallet.
And earphones.
How much do you love Sanrio? Sanrio?
My Melo earphones.
I've got an Airpod case in there.
But there's a drawback to this one.
I'm always in trouble on the train or something! I'm always in trouble on the train.
Here... here... here...
Here we go.
It's not good for me!It's not going to be like this!
When you fold this bag on the train like this
It's going to be like this.
It's like you're thinking about it.
Isn't this good? But it's too cute.
Isn't it awesome?
It's so cute! But I get excited every time I see it.
The earphone case is My Melo, and I'm using an air pod.
The rest of it is almost empty, to be honest.
But it looks good.
Does it look bad?
I don't know...
There's an area in there that looks bad.
Not the porch.
You know what it is? You know, in the bag.
It's this little detail zone.
There's a lot of stuff in there.
First of all, it's for the YouTube shoots we're doing today.
I've already mentioned this.
Earrings.
Oh! But I think I got this one, too.
Cinnamon! I know it's hard to see, but...
Cinnamon case
I bought it at a 100-yen shop.
I'm putting all the accessories called
I put them in one block.
And then there's
It's a weird wet wipe.
You were back in Kaboshima for a bit, right?
There.
At that time...
I went to the arcade.
The one there.
And...
Kirara skewers.
And gummies.
Fruit juice gummies.
I haven't opened it yet.
When I'm hungry.
I like gummy bears.
I put fruit juice in them.
And the elastic. For my hair. For my lessons.
I bought this one because it was all over social media. It's so cute.
It's cute. You just tie it on and it's stylish.
I have a bunch of these.
Kewpie Core Gold Alfage.
I've already taken one of these. They come in a pack of two.
I have a box of these at home so I can take a little with me.
Take away persistent fatigue
When I'm tired in the morning, when I'm tired at night, when I come down with fatigue...
It's totally for personal use.
That's what I drink.
And these iced lozenges.
I like them. They come in a candy.
I've always liked them. They come in different flavors.
But I've been rehearsing a lot, so I carry candies with me.
Oh!
Not at all...
This...
What's it look like?
It's, um...
Ah!
When you wear a light blue shirt for work or a recording session, when you sweat a little, the sweat from your armpits stands out, right?
You put this transparent film directly on your armpits.
Then you put it directly on your armpits, and the film holds the perspiration in place.
Nishio-san always carries a lot of them, so I put them in my bag.
And I don't even remember putting it in there.
Nagarekaku-san Direct Stick Peach
Cléd Peau Beauté sunscreen cream test product
I bet you drank some of that.
I just found this.
What's this?
I don't know.
A pen cap?
There's no pen in it.
It's really the last one.
I don't want to show you.
I don't understand.
I want to talk to Shichimi.
What's this?
I really don't know, but I found the seven spices.I really don't know, but I got some shichimi.
That's all!
Oh no, this is the part of my bag that's always the worst!
This is the only thing I didn't need. I might use some more shichimi.
If you guys ever want some shichimi, just let me know and I'll get you some.
I hope you enjoyed the contents of the skin.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
I'll see you later.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
mmm